Finding Aid for the Sidney Reznick Papers PASC.0297
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Scripts, project files, and printed materials, 1939-1990
  - Poor Soul "The Sidewalk Superintendent", undated (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Poor Soul "Camping Out", undated (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Poor Soul (Premises) (Theory and Construction), undated (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Poor Soul (Business), undated (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Poor Soul "Kite up a Tree", undated (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Skating Rink, undated (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Reggie - Ballet Stuff, undated (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Reggie - Drinking Gags, undated (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Reggie "The War Orphan", undated (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Reggie "Sports Car Salesman", undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Reggie "Sports Car Salesman", undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Reggie "Car Salesman", undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Reggie "The Artist", undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Reggie "African Material", undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Reggie "Ballet", undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Excavation, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Reggie "Gags", undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Horse, undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Power of Positive Hypnosis, undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Reggie "Premises and Bits", undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Rudy the Repairman, undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Rudy the Repairman "HiFi- Hi-Jinx", undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Norton Lines, undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Insults, undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - The Honeymooners (Premises and Bits), undated (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - The Honeymooners (Plot Outliners), undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - The Honeymooners (Premises), undated (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - The Honeymooners ("Are You From Texas"), undated (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - The Honeymooners ("The Rich Uncle"), undated (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - The Honeymooners (Script), undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - The Honeymooners ("The Steamer Trunk"), undated (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - The Honeymooners (As Used), undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Comedy Spots, 1963-1965 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Rum Dum, undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Reggie, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Comedy spots, 1963-1965 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Comedy spots and photocopied stills, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Agreements, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Letters, undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Film Stills, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Jackie Gleason Monologue - "The Ray Bloch Story", undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Gary Moore, undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - "That Wonderful Year", undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Reject File (Garry Moore), undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - "The Garry Moore Show", undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Scripts, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Arthur Peck, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Jackie Gleason, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - JG Blackouts, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Jackie Gleason, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Fenwick Babbitt, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Jackie Gleason, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Joe, The Bartender, undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Monologue - Joe, The Bartender, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - #16, 1960 January 10 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Monologue, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Don Rickels Special, undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Commercials, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Production Numbers, undated (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Bits, undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Bits, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - The Fabulous Zoo of Blackouts, undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Comedy Spots, undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Gags, undated (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Gags/Bits, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Removed from loose bound notebook - no label
  - Intro's, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Monologue, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Routines (Completed), undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Routines, 1961/1962 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Routines, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Presentations TV Shows, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Bad Taste, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Stories, undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Stories, undated (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Stories, undated (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Nostalgia, undated (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Night Club (Risque), undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Comedians, undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - The Quiz and Game Show Book, undated (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Game Shows, 1948-1967 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - "The Facts of Life", 1979 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - The Facts of Life (Game), undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - The Facts of Life (Illustrations), undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - "The Facts of Life", undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - "The Facts of Life", undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - "The Facts of Life", undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - "The Facts of Life", undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - "Frammis", undated (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - "Facts of Life", 1974 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - "Frammis" - Legal, undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - "Frammis" (2nd Revision), undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - "Frammis" - Completed Rounds, undated (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - "Frammis" (1968 Submission), undated (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - The "Frammis" Game (Cartoon), undated (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - "Frammis", undated (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - "Frammis" (Impersonator), undated (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - "Frammis", undated (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - "Frammis" (Words), undated (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - "Frammis" - #2, undated (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - "Frammis" (See "Padiddle!"), 1973 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - "Padiddle!", 1989 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - "Padiddle!", 1981 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Research and Notes
  - "Padiddle!" (Smart Money Presentation), undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - "Padiddle!", undated (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - "Padiddle!" (Revised), undated (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - "Padiddle!", undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - "Padiddle!", 1976 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - "Padiddle!", 1976-1977 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - "Padiddle!", 1978 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Honeymoonus Interuptus, undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - T.O.W.G. Jill St. John, undated (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - "The Other Woman" Game, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - "The Other Woman" - Release from Frank Cooper, undated (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - T.O.W.G. Legal, undated (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - T.O.W.G. (Continued), undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - "Four-O" (Legal), undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - "Four-O", undated (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - To Be Photostated, undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - "Foursies", 1987 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - "Foursies", 1993 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - "Four of a Kind" (Legal), undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - "Mad Movies", undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - "Mad Movies", undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - "The Gold Rush" 2nd Revision (Presentation), undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Crapple Corners "Hushed Whispers", undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - "I'll Buy That!" Game Show, undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - "Place the Face" (or "Your Attention, Please"), 1969 September 6 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - "Mystery Voice Board", undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - "The Code Game" Gags, undated (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - "Snap Judgement" (Celebrity Teammate), undated (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - What's Missing, undated (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - "Zilch!" (Comedy Game Show), undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Set: 4 Panelists (Art Work), undated (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Game Board, undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Duck, undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Game Board, undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Whoopee, undated (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Artwork, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - "Fractured Funnies" (Comedy Game Show), undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - "Tic-Tac-Toe" ("Three to Win"), undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - "Win Your Freedom", undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - "Win Your Freedom", undated (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - "The King of Comedy", 1940 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - "The King of Comedy" (Win Your Letter), 1976 September 14 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - "The King of Comedy", 1968 September 16 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - "The King of Comedy", 1973 March 20 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - "The King of Comedy" (Army Grant, Ralph Andrews Productions, Inc.), undated (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - "The King of Comedy" Presentation, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - "The King of Comedy", 1989 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - The Great American Pinball Game, undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Gameshows, undated (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Art-Ben Development "Whatchamacallit", undated (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - "Whatchamacallit" (Completed Names, Titles, etc.), undated (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - "Whatchamacallit" - Playword: Bonus Round, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - "Whatchamacallit" Script, undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - "Whatchamacallit" "Name Bank" "Star Bank" "Pot Bank", undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - "Whatchamacallit" Negotiations (Art and Ben), undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Playword Bonus Round (Completed), undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - "Whatchamacallit" (A and B Presentation), 1969 May 8 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - "Whatchamacallit" (Format), undated (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - "Whatchamacallit", undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - "Whatchamacallit", 1972 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - "Whatchamacallit" - "Name Bank", undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - "Whatchamacallit", 1971 October (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - "Whatchamacallit" (Development), 1969 May (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - "Whatchamacallit" Art and Ben (Runthrough Material), undated (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - "Whatchamacallit" (Revised) (includes pictures), undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - "Whatchamacallit" (Word Bank Version), undated (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Precedent for "Whatchamacallit", undated (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - "Whatchamacallit", undated (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - "Whatchamacallit", 1969 February (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Bonus-Blitz-Go-Go, undated (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - "Whatchamacallit" (Format Variations), 1969 April 28 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Top Your Pop, undated (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Who Do You Think You Are, undated (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Garry - Who Do You Think You Are, undated (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - "Sez Who!" ("Hearing is Believing"), undated (Box 63, Folder 24)
    Legal - Contract - Budget - Etc
  - "Sez Who!" (Look in filing cabinet #2 - Under "Who" - TV Version), undated (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - "Sez Who!" Panel - MC Suggestions, undated (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - "Sez Who!", undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!", 1981 June, 1982 February (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!", undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!", undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Gospel According To, undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - "We Saw It Happen", undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - "What If?" Comedy Panel Reality Show, undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - "In Your Face!", undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - "A Little Night Comedy" (Latenite Talk-Variety), undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - "What's the Beef?", undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Amateur Fashion Design Show, undated (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - "My Favorite Wife" (Revised), undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - "My Favorite Wife", undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - "The Truth Fairy" (Comedy with an Edge), undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Small Talk, undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - "The Flip Side", undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - "Stand-Up Comics Olympics", undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - "Mr. Comedy", undated (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - "The Moppsy Twins", undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - "Young Mr Gabriel", undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - WGAW Fund 51, undated (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Western Union, Please, undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - "Mama Don't Allow!", undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - "An Evening at Grauman's Chinese", undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - TV Or Not TV, undated (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - "Hit It Munificent", undated (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Buster and the Four-Eyed Ogre, undated (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - (Star) and the Four-Eyed Ogre, undated (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Ballet (Star) and the Four-Eyed Ogre, undated (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Make Love to a Star; Love Star, undated (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - "Why I Want to be Rich", undated (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - "The Professionals" ("Spies R Us"), undated (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - "Was It Good for You Too?" (Ex-"Slim"), undated (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - "Thank Heaven!", undated (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - "Sex Comedy Playhouse" (a la "Carol Burnett Show"), undated (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - "Fu Manchu" - "Sax Rohher" Biographies, undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - "The Hollywood Show Boat", undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Got News For You - Good,Bad, undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - "The People Versus...", undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - "(Burt Reynolds) Looks at Sex", undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - The Sea Rangers, undated (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - "Iffy Iffy World ("S'posin")", undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - "What Do You Do For Kicks?", undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - "Zingo!", 1967 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - "Zingo!", 1995 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - "Niki Zhivago Comedy Hour", undated (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Half of 60 Minutes, 1980 June 10 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Advertising Irvin Graham, undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - "What Did Famous People"... Wedding Night, undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - "Jewish Mothers of Famous People" or "What If", undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - "Jewish Mothers of Famous People", undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Obie, My Boy, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Obie, My Boy, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Obie, My Boy, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Obie Story Suggestions, undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Here's Obie, undated (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Personal + Biographical, undated (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - WGAW Registrations, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Registrations - WGAW, undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Program Idea Registrations - WGAW, undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - WGA/Authors' League Registrations, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - WGA Registrations, circa 1960s (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - WGA Registrations, circa 1970s (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - WGA Registrations, circa 1980s (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - WGA Registrations, circa 1990s (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Income Ledger, 1962-1976 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Agreements, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Testimonials, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Letter to Reznick from Sgt Ralph Cohen w/attachments, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1939-1986 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Writers Annual Awards Dinner Programs, 1967 and 1973 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Cartoon World, undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Projectors - Product Manuals, undated (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Printed Sheet Music, undated (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Writers Show, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Hollywood Censor Sketch, undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Everything You Wanted to Know About, undated (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - "Encyclopedia of Superheroes", undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Lines (Saves), undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Lines, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Upcoming Presentations (1), undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Masters, undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Movie and TV Story Lines, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Motion Picture Side Plots, undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Comedy Material, undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Comedy Concepts, undated (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - The Quest, undated (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Go For Broke - Game Show Designs, undated (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Photograph of Resnick with others, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Original Artwork: Baldwin, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Original Artwork: Sean Harrison "The Sea Rangers", undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Sez Who - Quiz Show of the Year award certificate, undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Original Artwork, undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - "The Other Woman Game", undated (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - "Other Woman" Scorecards, undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who" Artwork, undated (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Obie My Boy, undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Series 2: Sound recordings, 1947-1968
  The series consists of a small number of phonograph records produced in circa 1947. The works appear to be commercially produced comedy skits, collected by Reznick, featuring Burns and Allen, Edgar Bergen and Charlie McCarthy, Fiber McGee and Molly, and Ed "Archie" Gardner and musical recordings featuring musical performer Gertrude Lawrence. This series also includes 120 radio transcription discs and 10 audiotapes.
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Burns and Allen, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    What Every Young Bride Should Know, pt 2; What Every Old Husband Should Know, pt 1.
  - Ed "Archie" Gardner, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    Two Top Gruskin, pt. 1; Flatbush On The Thames, pt. 2.
  - Burns and Allen, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    The French Long Underwear Maker pt. 2; Sugar Throat Sings Again.
  - Burns and Allen, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    What Every Young Bride Should Know, pt 1; What Every Old Husband Should Know, pt 2.
  - Burns and Allen, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    The French Long Underwear Maker pt. 1; Gracie Discovers A Movie Star.
  - Ed "Archie" Gardner, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    Deems Dem and Dose, pt 1; The Sympathetic Part, pt 2.
  - Ed "Archie" Gardner, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    Two Top Gruskin, pt. 2; Flatbush On The Thames, pt. 1.
  - Ed "Archie" Gardner, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    Deems Dem and Dose, pt 2; The Sympathetic Part, pt 1.
  - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    The Three Little Pigs; The Bakery Man.
  - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    Glass Blowing; Under Wear By Mail Oder.
  - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    A Lesson in Life Savings; Ventriloquism Exposed.
  - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy; Edgar Bergen and Mortimer Snerd, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    Little Red Riding Hood; A Grammar Lesson.
  - Fiber McGee and Molly, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    A Visit to the Dairy, pt 1; A Facinatin Hunk of History.
  - Fiber McGee and Molly, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    A Visit to the Dairy, pt 2; Its All Greek.
  - Fiber McGee and Molly, circa 1947 (Box 9)
    A Few Notes on Piano Tuning, part 2; Strictly Off The Record.
  - Gertrude Lawrence, undated (Box 9)
    My Ship; Jenny.
  - Gertrude Lawrence, undated (Box 9)
    Princess of Pure Delight; Glamour Music.
  - Gertrude Lawrence, undated (Box 9)
    One Life To Live; This Is New.
  - Salesman's Conquest; Salesman's Dilemma, undated (Box 9)
  - All Star Revue (Durante), 1951 November 3 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Today Show Interview, 1959 December (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Today Show Interview, 1959 December (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - All Star Revue (Durante), 1951 December 29 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - All Star Revue (Durante), 1951 November 3 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - All Star Revue (Durante), 1951 December 29 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - All Star Revue (Durante), 1952 January 26 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - All Star Revue (Durante), 1952 January 27 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Phil Silvers Show, 1947 June 25 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Phil Silvers Show, 1947 July 2 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Phil Silvers Show, 1947 July 16 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Phil Silvers Show, 1947 July 30 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Phil Silvers Show, 1947 August (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Phil Silvers Show, 1947 August (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Phil Silvers Show, 1947 August (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Phil Silvers Show, 1947 October (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Phil Silvers Show, 1947 October (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - "3 On a Honeymoon" Starring Phil Baker, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
    10 extra envelopes
  - "Sez Who!" Audition, 1957 June 12 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - "Hearing is Believing" Audition, 1953 May 25 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Young Mr. Gabriel Part 2, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Voice Tests "Young Mr. Gabriel", undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Young Mr. Gabriel Part 1, undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" Audition, 1957 May 24 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #1, 1957 July 14 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #2, 1957 July 21 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #3, 1957 July 28 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #4, 1957 August 4 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #5, 1957 August 11 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" #6, 1957 August 18 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #7, 1957 August 25 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #8, 1957 September 1 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #9, 1957 September 8 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #9, 1957 September (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #10, 1957 September 22 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" #11, 1957 September 29 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #12, 1957 October 6 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #13, 1957 October 13 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #14, 1957 October 20 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #15, 1957 October 27 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #16, 1957 November 3 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #17, 1957 November 9 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #18, 1957 November 16 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #19, 1957 November 23 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #20, 1957 December 1 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #21, 1957 December 8 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" #22, 1957 December 15 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - "Sez Who!" #23, 1957 December 22 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #24, 1957 December 29 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #25, 1958 January 5 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #26, 1958 January 12 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #27, 1958 January 19 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #28, 1958 January 26 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" #29, 1958 February 2 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #30, 1958 February 9 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #31, 1958 February 16 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #32, 1958 February 23 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #34, 1958 March 2 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #35, 1958 March 9 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" #36, 1958 March 16 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #37, 1958 March 23 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #38, 1958 March 30 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #39, 1958 April 6 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #40, 1958 April 13 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #41, 1958 April 20 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" #42, 1958 May 4 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #43, 1958 May 11 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #44, 1958 May 18 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #45, 1958 May 25 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #46, 1958 June 2 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #47, 1958 June 8 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" #48, 1958 June 15 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #49, 1958 June 22 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #50, 1958 June 29 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #51, 1958 July 6 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #52, 1958 July 13 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #53, 1958 July 20 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" #54, 1958 July 27 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #55, 1958 August 3 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #56, 1958 August 10 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #57, 1958 August 17 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #58, 1958 August 24 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #59, 1958 August 31 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" #60, 1958 September 7 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #61, 1958 September 14 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #62, 1958 September 21 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #63, 1958 September 28 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #64, 1958 October 5 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #65, 1958 October 12 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" #66, 1958 October 19 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #67, 1958 October 26 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #68, 1958 November 2 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - "Sez Who!" #69, 1958 November 9 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - "Sez Who!" #70, 1958 November 16 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - "Sez Who!" #71, 1958 November 23 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - "Sez Who!" #72, 1958 November 30 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - "Sez Who!" #73, 1958 December 7 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - "Sez Who!" #74, 1958 December 14 (Box 89, Folder 3)